http://www.ssl4net.com/privacy-policy

SSL Certificate Management SiteSsl4net
SSL Certificate for Networks and NetworkingTechnologyTrial and Free SSL CertificatesVendors - ProvidersComodoDigiCertEntrustGeoTrustGlobalSignGo DaddyNetwork SolutionsThawteTrustwaveVeriSignSSL Certificate for Your NeedSSL Certificate for Mail Servers (MTA)SSL Certificate for Web ServersBuy SSL CertificatesGoDaddy SSL CertificatesEntrust SSL CertificatesNetwork Solutions SSL CertificatesThawte SSL CertificatesVeriSign SSL CertificatesGeoTrust SSL CertificatesExtended Validation (EV) SSL CertificatesOrganization Validated (OV) SSL CertificatesUnified Communications (UC) / SAN SSL CertificatesDomain Validated (DV) SSL Certificates
LinksEntrust SSL CertificatesGo Daddy SSL CertificatesVeriSign SSL Certificates Network Solutions SSL CertificatesGeoTrust SSL CertificatesThawte SSL Certificates
Privacy Policy
Information CollectionPersonal information is collected from customers only after obtaining consent, which is obtained when customers are prompted for information when subscribing to the services, by using a SSL4NET website, downloading a product, or requesting further information. Personally-identifiable information is not collected when a user simply browses the website. SSL4NET may contact customers about offers and opportunities from SSL4NET or its business partners, to conduct surveys, and gather feedback. This privacy statement does not extend to any information that is beyond the control of SSL4NET.ServicesEnrolling in SSL4NEt's subscription service may require a customer to provide certain personal information and enter into a Subscriber Agreement. Nothing herein is intended to modify the terms in the Subscriber Agreement.Product DownloadDownloading a product will often require the input of personal information. This information will be used by SSL4NET or its affiliates to contact the customer about SSL4NET's products and services, including product updates and associated promotional material. This information may also be used as collated general demographic information to improve SSL4NET's products and services.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on a computer's hard disk containing information about the owner. SSL4NET may employ the use of cookies for measuring the success of advertising and affiliate network membership. Our partners may use cookies. SSL4NET does not exercise any access or control of such cookies.SSL4NET's websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), to evaluate the use of the SSL4NET site. Google Analytics places a third party cookie on your computer that is then used to compile reports of visitor traffic and internet usage. Google analytics does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor and only collects aggregate data.Log FilesSSL4NET uses log files comprising of non-personally identifiable information to analyze trends, administer the site, track movements throughout the site, calculate the number of document and file downloads, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.SharingSSL4NET will share aggregated demographic and other information with our partners and affiliates. Information provided to SSL4NET will be protected by SSL4NET and not sold or rented to any unrelated third parties without the express consent of the information provider, except that SSL4NET may disclose data to its affiliates and business partners who have established similar privacy standards, when legally obligated to do so, or if disclosure is required to protect the rights over SSL4NET, SSL4NET's customers, or the users of SSL4NET's services. SSL4NET may also share aggregate demographic data that does not contain any personally identifiable information.Validation is an essential step in receiving a Certificate from SSL4NET CA. This validation may require verifying your information with a third party as described in the SSL4NET CPS. SSL4NET CA may disclose the information provided to the extent necessary to verify the certificate application.External LinksThe SSL4NET website contains links to external websites which are outside the scope of this privacy statement. SSL4NET is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and does not control the accuracy of information displayed by such websites.Forums, Bulletin Boards, Testimonials, Chat Rooms, and SurveysPersonal information submitted through a forum, bulletin board, testimonial, or chat room operated by SSL4NET may be collected, used, and read by third parties, including other users. SSL4NET is not responsible for any information submitted through these services. We occasionally request information from customers via surveys. Participation in these customer surveys is voluntary. Survey information is used to improve this web site and our services and products.Refer a Friend ProgramSSL4NET provides the ability to send emails to your email contacts. You can use the Refer a Friend page to log into your mail account and send a message to your friends. This message may be customized by you. SSL4NET does not store any of the information entered by you as part of the email process.SecuritySSL4NET protects information both online and off-line. The transmission of information, including any payment information, is encrypted and protected using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). Stored customer information is kept in a secure environment where access is restricted to employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example billing administration or the development team). Employees are required to use password-protected screen-savers and keep their computers up-to-date.Choice / Opt outCustomers may occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals from SSL4NET or may receive informational newsletters. Customers are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information used for purposes not directly related to the SSL4NET service at the point where the information is requested. Customers may also elect not to receive additional promotional communications using the opt-out link provided in each promotional email or by emailing pr@ssl4net.com. Customers may not opt-out of receiving service announcement updates as they contain important security information about the services.AmendmentsSSL4NET reserves the right to amend this privacy statement at any time. Any amendment will be made by posting the changes to the website. Customers must check the website periodically to be aware of any changes to the privacy statement. Your continued use of the website or SSL4NET product or service constitutes your acceptance of those changes.
Refund Policy             Privacy Policy
Sign in|Recent Site Activity|Report Abuse|Print Page|Powered By Google Sites
